rajasthanroyals.com 2019-03-23

# Privacy Policy - Rajasthan Royals

### Introduction

This website is operated by Royal Multisport Private Limited (Formerly known as Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Limited).. At Royal Multisport Private Limited, we are very sensitive to the privacy concerns of visitors to our website, since many of the visitors to this website may include children. We take care that the content posted on this website is appropriate for their viewing and/or use. This Privacy Statement outlines the way in which Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd gathers and uses information relating to you, the user of the Rajasthan Royals website (“User”). By using this website, the User consents to the use (including transfer) of information as described below

### What information do we collect?

We collect the following information from visitors to our website: information such as IP addresses, information relating to what pages have been viewed (e.g. using cookies as described further below) and personal information volunteered by you (via online or offline registration forms), such as name, contact details, e-mail address, postal address, telephone/mobile number, your gender, date of birth etc. and whether you have chosen to receive future communications from Rajasthan Royals and Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd partners.

On some of our web pages, you may be able to enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, or subscribe to one of our services such as our newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities or otherwise voluntarily provide information to us. In connection with certain online/offline competitions and contests, you may be invited to submit personal information that we will collect only when you voluntarily provide it.

### How do we use your information?

We use the information we collect on the website to help us understand how the website is being used and to allow us to communicate with you. Such information will enable us to communicate with you on any matter relating to Rajasthan Royals, [including the provision by us or selected third parties of relevant information, goods and/or services in which we think you may be interested, unless you have chosen not to receive such material]. We may on occasion combine information we receive online with other records to enhance our ability to notify you of the details of Rajasthan Royals and our other services that we think will be of interest to you.

You can (subject to payment of an appropriate fee) request a copy of information held about you at any time by contacting [admin@rajasthanroyals.com](mailto:admin@rajasthanroyals.com). In the event that the operations of Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd are transferred to or integrated with another operation, your details may be disclosed to our advisors and transferee of the operations of Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd.

### Cookies

The Rajasthan Royals website uses cookies. A cookie is a small file containing an identity code. Your computer accepts the cookie and stores it and when you next visit the website, the code is retrieved, allowing individual visitors or computers to be recognized. Cookies are used for a variety of purposes including providing personalized web pages and recognizing your choice of language. Cookies do not cause harm to your computer but if you do wish to stop your computer accepting cookies, you can go to the help section of your Internet browser (e.g. Internet Explorer or Mozilla) where you will find information on how to do this. Please note that if you disable cookies, you may be unable to access some customized features on our website. Cookies do not collect or contain your name or email address.

### Internet Security

We ensure that personal data of visitors on this website is subject to appropriate security.

We may share information about visitors to this site in aggregate with third parties including advertisers, business partners and sponsors, to understand the trends and patterns on the Website and manage and improve our business relationships.

We may share personal information with third parties to administer and process your requests. These parties shall use the information solely in conjunction with the specific services they provide for us (e.g. fulfillment of an order of a newsletter, responding to your question or comment, providing a sweepstakes prize, deployment of a consumer survey, investigation of a complaint, and so on.).

Our agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to disclose any personal information as needed if such information is requested by law enforcement agencies or if we are required to do so by law, regulation, subpoena, court order, or by a government entity. We also may disclose personal information to third parties if we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to conduct investigations of possible breaches of law, to cooperate in any legal investigation, or to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the terms of use of our site.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about a User in the event that we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party. We also reserve the right to share information within Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd and its business partners.

Although, we will endeavour to meet the requirements of the Internet Security policy envisaged under this section, we cannot accept any responsibility for any loss, disruption or damage to your data or your computer system that may occur whilst using material derived from this website. As best practice, we also strongly recommend that you regularly run an anti-virus programme on all material downloaded from the Internet.

### Updating your information and opting out

If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example, if you change your e-mail address or name or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to [admin@rajasthanroyals.com](mailto:admin@rajasthanroyals.com). Alternatively, you can send a letter to The Data Controller, Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd Management Private Limited, 906 Windfall, Sahar Plaza Complex, Mathuradas Vasanji Road, J. B. Nagar, Andheri (E), Mumbai – 400 059. All e-mail communications from Jaipur IPL Cricket Private Ltd will include an unsubscribe facility.

### Other websites

Our website may contain links to other web sites that are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other websites using the links provided, the operators of these websites may collect information from you, which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. Other websites may collect and treat information collected differently, so we encourage you to carefully read and review the privacy policy for each website you visit. We will not be responsible for any information that you may provide to such websites accessible through our website.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We will also e-mail you should we make any changes, so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. By using this website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and signify your assent to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you do not agree with any term of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use, please do not use this site or submit any personally identifiable information.

### How can you contact Rajasthan Royals?

We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. Please feel free to contact us if you have any queries or comments.
